欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
《比利小子》前情提要
Previously on Billy the Kid
不许进入我家中
Do not come in my house.
他们杀了所有人 比利
They killed everyone, Billy.
我知道
Iknow.
我会为你家人报仇的 我发誓
I will avenge your family's death, I swear.
好吧 我们要接管这个镇子
AII right. We're takin' over the town.
我们要恢复林肯镇的法律和秩序
We're gonna restore law and order in Lincoln.
所以我们必须干掉浩世集团
But we have to take out The House to do it.
看来监管者已经控制了市中心
It would seem that The Regulators control
和墨西哥区的大部分地区
most of the downtown and the Mexican quarter.
我会叫几个副手过来
I'm callin' in my deputies.
他们一到我就让他们去
As soon as they arrive, I'll send them
汤斯顿商行
to the Tunstall Store.
来吧 孩子们
Here we go, boys.
监管者和墨西哥人
The Regulators with the Mexicans
构成了一支65人左右的武装力量
constitute a significant force of around 65.
可我们还凑不齐三分之一
Right now that's a third more than we can muster.
治安官说的对 比利小子知道我们下落
Sheriff's right. If The Kid wants us,
他随时都能找过来
he knows where we are.
除非 除非我们剑走偏锋
Unless. we change the odds.
达德利上校 我是新任治安官
Colonel Dudley, it's the new sheriff.
我带来一份阿克塞尔
I have here a proclamation
总督的公告 要求所有武装人员
from Governor Axtell. It commands all armed men
在美国军队召唤前 就地解散
to disband, so long as U. S. Army can be summoned.
我们决不投降 我现在相信了
We must never surrender. I believe that now.
我们在为正义而战 为崇高的事业而战
We're fighting for a good cause, a noble cause.
加勒特治安官 好样的
Sheriff Garrett, good man!
你来得正是时候
You came just in time.
我命令你们所有人马上回家
I am ordering all of you to go home, now.
本镇正在开始宵禁 解禁时间末知
This town is under permanent curfew.
达德利上校才代表这个国家的真正律法
Colonel Dudley is the real law in this country.
只要我们跟他解释
And when we explain to him- -
不会有什么不同的 麦克斯温太太
It won't make any difference, Mrs. McSween.
你和我 我们是伙伴关系
You and me, we're partners here,
加勒特治安官 我只有一个愿望
and all I want, Sheriff Garrett,
就是看到那个比利臭小子
is nothing more than to see that Billy the fuckin' Kid
挂在绞刑架上
hangin'on the end of a rope.
把那个放楼上去
That goes upstairs, please.
小心点 这是我母亲的东西
Be careful, it was my mother's.
比利 真没有别的办法了么
Billy, isn't there something else we can do?
我们就不能举面白旗
I mean, can't we go and take a white flag
去找上校谈谈吗
and go up and talk to the Colonel?
你听到了 整个镇子都被封锁 要实行宵禁
You heard him. The whole town is on lockdown. It's a curfew.
那我们为什么不离开呢 离开林肯
Why don't we try and leave, get out of Lincoln?
查理 我们不能再跑了
Charlie, we're not runnin' again.
我只是不希望大家惹毛美国军队
I just don't want us gettin' cut down in the street
被横尸街头 但我们不会放弃的
by the U. S. Army, but we're not quittin'.
我们都会死的 比利
Are we all gonna die, Billy?
不会的 汤姆
No, Tom.
你怎么能这么肯定
How can you be so sure?
因为我正竭尽全力
Because I'm doin' everything in my power
确保这不会发生
to make sure that doesn't happen.
好了 去帮忙在房子
Now, go help put the barricades
南边设置路障
in the south side of the house.
干点有用的事
Make yourself useful.
有人来了
Someone's comin'.
是谁
Who's that?
我是克雷医生 还记得我吗
It's Dr. Clay. You remember me?
慢一点
Slowly.
哈 我当然记得
Ha. Why, of course I do.
不介意我们进来吧 麦克斯温先生
Mind if we come in, Mr. McSween?
当然 请进 请进
Yes, come in. Come in.
没关系 没关系
It's all right. It's all right.
什么风把您吹来了 医生
What brings you here, doc?
你好啊 比利
Hello, Billy.
请允许我介绍一下内人 爱丽丝
Uh, may I introduce my wife, Alice.
她是个护士
She's a nurse.
我们昨天听到些消息 觉得可能会有麻烦
We've come because we listened to what was said yesterday,
所以才过来的
and think there might be trouble.
如果真是这样 你可能会需要我们
In which case, you might need us.
你们确定要以身涉险吗
Are you sure you want to put yourself in the way of danger?
让我来说吧 麦克斯温先生
If I can speak for both of us, Mr. McSween,
我们站在你这边
we are on your side.
我们相信监管者 相信你们的大业
We believe in The Regulators and in your cause.
我们不能袖手旁观 什么也不做
We simply could not stand by and do nothing.
谢谢你 谢谢两位
Well, thank you...both.
克雷医生 我来帮您拿帽子 愿上帝保佑你
Dr. Clay. Let me take your hat. God bless you.
谢谢了
Thank you.
朋友们
Friends,
我们仍需要加强
we still need to tighten
对监管者据点的包围
the ring around The Regulators' stronghold,
也就是麦克斯温大宅
which is to say, McSween's house.
我们可不想让任何一人逃走 好吗
We don't want any of them slippin' away, do we?
同时 在我的敦促下
Meanwhile, with my encouragement,
加勒特治安官拿到了逮捕麦克斯温
Sheriff Garrett has obtained fresh warrants
比利小子和其他监管者的
for the arrest of McSween, Billy the Kid and the rest
逮捕令
of The Regulators
原因是涉嫌共谋杀害布雷迪治安官
for complicity in the murder of Sheriff Brady.
现在 看在新任治安官的份上
Now, for the sake of our new sheriff,
我们得去执行这张搜查令
we're gonna try to serve these warrants,
因为从今往后 一切行为都要在法律
because everything now has got to be done within the letter
允许的范围内进行
of the fuckin'law.
我们也绝不会做什么违法的事
We wouldn't dream of doing anything unlawful,
对吗 小子们
now would we, boys?
地狱会让他绝望的
Ain't no hope in hell
比利会投降的
Billy is just gonna surrender.
这得他来决定 不是吗
Well, that's up to him, now, isn't it?
他要是不这么做 就是真的傻
He would be a fool not to, anyway.
杰西 来一下
Jesse, come.
我亲自把达德利上校
I personally invited
从军营里请来
Colonel Dudley out of his shite tent
下榻进这里的客房
to stay in one of the guest rooms here,
毕竟客房要比帐篷舒服多了
where he's gonna be far more comfortable.
你觉得上校站在我们这边吗
You think the Colonel is on our side?
加勒特治安官
Sheriff Garrett asked him down
是代表法制派请他出山
on behalf of the Law and Order Party,
来解决这个问题的 所以没错
to sort this thing out, so yeah,
我觉得他会站我们这边
I figure that's where his sympathies lie.
达德利上校 早上好
Colonel Dudley, good mornin'.
治安官 谢谢你们
Sheriff. Thank you, boys.
莱利先生邀请我住进家里
Mr. Riley has kindly invited me to stay at the House.
他真是太有心了
Well, that is, uh, mighty civil of him.
我想请你帮个忙
I have a favor to ask.
又要帮忙 治安官
Another, Sheriff?
我有一张麦克斯温先生
I have some warrants to serve
和监管者成员的逮捕令
on Mr. McSween and members of The Regulators,
理由是他们涉嫌谋杀我的上一任
for their role in the murder of my predecessor.
我得确保他们安全移交到位
I need to make sure they're handed over safely.
也就是说
Which means?
也许法治党的成员可以
Members of the Law and Order Party might be allowed
暂时解除宵禁 掩护那些要去
to break curfew, cover those who have been given the task
麦克斯温房子里实行抓捕的
of delivering the warrants to the people inside
人马
the McSween house.
我希望你能通融一下
I hoped you might be able to facilitate that.
我不想让你的人陷入危险
I don't wanna endanger any of your men, obviously.
很好 你得到我的允许了
Very well. You have my permission.
我会派几个士兵
I will have some of my soldiers
护送你的人过去
escort your men while the warrants are delivered.
我非常感激 谢谢你
I'm very grateful. Thank you.
治安官 你不要认为
Sheriff, you mustn't think for a moment
我这么做是在偏袒你们
that I've picked sides here.
陆军一向保持中立
The Army remains neutral.
我们是来恢复和平的 仅此而已
We are here to restore the peace, that's all.
当然
Of course.
我也是
That's what I'm doing too.
里面有人吗
Anybody home?
出来吧 麦克斯温
Come on out, McSween.
蹲下
Get down.
听着
Listen here,
我们有逮捕令 来抓麦克斯温
we got warrants for McSween's arrest,
和一切参与杀害布雷迪治安官的人
and anyone else involved in the killing of Sheriff Brady.
我决不投降
I will never surrender.
别忘了 我也有警察发的逮捕令
And remember, I have warrants for the posse's arrest.
你残忍地杀了约翰·汤斯顿
You killed John Tunstall in cold blood.
我挺想看看那张搜查令的 麦克斯温
I'd sure like to see those warrants, McSween!
我们有搜查令的 你个狗娘养的
We got warrants in our guns, you son of a bitch!
你在里面吗 比利
You in there, Billy?
你好吗
How are ya?
挺好的 谢谢你 杰西
Very well, thank you, Jesse.
但我们不会出来的
But we ain't comin'out.
随你便 比利
Suit yourself, Billy.
这是你的搜查令
Here are your warrants!
小子们
Boys. -
我们无路可走了
We're trapped.
不一定
Not necessarily.
如果达德利信守保持中立的诺言
If Dudley sticks to his word and stays neutral,
我们可能会被护送出去
we may get escorted out of here.
比利
Billy...
我觉得我不可能活着离开这里了
I don't think I'm getting out of this place alive.
你总怎么想就不会
Not if you keep talkin' like that, you won't.
加勒特有暗示过你
Did. ...did Garrett give you any indication
他会帮我们吗
that he was gonna help us?
我只知道 当年跟我一起当牛仔的加勒特
All I know is the Garrett I used to ride with
不会留我在这里等死
wouldn't leave me here to hang.
好吧 总算有点希望
Well, here's hopin'.
可他要是真这么做了呢
But if he does?
那样的话 我们再另想办法
If he does, we'll find another way.
我们总能想到办法
We always do.
我们得做好面对所有可能的准备
We just got to be prepared for anything.
下凡吧 加布里埃尔
♪Come down, Gabriel ♪
吹响你的号角吧
♪Blow your horn ♪
在清晨叫我回家吧
♪Call me home In the early morn'j
把马车往家的方向赶
♪` Send the chariot Home this way ♪
来吧 把我拉回家 留下来
♪Come and haul me Home to stay ♪
天使与我相遇在十字路口 与我相遇
♪Angels meet me At the crossroads, meet me ♪
让我这个罪人免费通行
♪Don't charge a sinner Any toll ♪
天使与我相遇
♪Angels meet me ♪
在十字路囗 与我相遇
♪ In the crossroads, meet me ♪
天使与我相遇
♪Angels meet me ♪
在十字路口 与我相遇
♪In the crossroads, meet me ♪
天使与我相遇在十字路口 与我相遇
♪Angels meet me In the crossroads, meet me ♪
让罪人免费通行
♪Don't charge a sinner Any toll ♪♪
他们拒绝接受逮捕令
They refused to accept the warrant.
他们不会出来的
They are not comin' out.
所以我们得把他们弄出来
So we need to get them out.
他们是一个棘手又迫在眉睫的危险
They're a clear and present danger.
他们是杀手 是歹徒
They're killers! They're outlaws!
他们是通缉犯 上校
They're wanted men, Colonel.
我知道
I know.
那你一定知道 你和加勒特治安官
Oh, you know? Well, then, you and Sheriff Garrett
得过去把他们弄出来
need to go and get them the fuck out.
你这是让我拿手下的生命去冒险
You would have me risk the lives of my men?
去做明令禁止的事
Doing something that I am forbidden to do?
莱利先生 我要跟你说多少遍
Mr. Riley, how many times must I tell you?
我是来维护和平的 不是来选边站的
I'm here to bring peace, not to pick sides.
好的 理解
Sure. Understood.
他说了什么
0 What did he say?
跟之前一样
Same as always.
立场不变 也不会出兵
Not gonna change. Not gonna move.
是的
No.
但我会出兵
But I am.
胡安·派特伦的儿子来了
你好啊
Hola.
你好 你是胡安的儿子吧
是我叫迭戈
告诉我那边出什么事了听说军队也加入了
他们都安全吗 比利 查理 所有人呢
镇子目前在军队控制下
我父亲和墨西哥人都待在自己家 我好不容易才逃了出来
但大多数白人佬都被困在麦克斯温先生的家里
我父亲想让我告诉你 军队已经封锁了道路
非常感谢
保重
我们必须走
去哪儿
去林肯
我们应该再找些女人跟我们一起骑马去找胡安·帕特仑
如果比利和查理有麻烦 我们应该去帮忙
你在干什么呢 莱利
What are you doing, Riley?
-嘿  -嘿
Hey. Hey.
莱利在打鬼主意
Riley's up to something.
去告诉比利 做好准备
Go tell Billy and them to get ready.
-是的 先生  -沿着小巷走
Yes, sir. Stick to the alleys.
-别让人看见  -是 先生
- Stay out of sight, all right? - Yes, sir.
嘿
Hey.
带上这个
Take this.
快去快回
Go quick.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
啊 该死
Ah, shit.
现在是宵禁 年轻人
We're under curfew, young man.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
不去哪儿
I'm not goin' anywhere.
-我得逮捕你  -放开我
- I'm arresting you. Leave me alonel
什么动静
What was that? !
该死
Goddamn it!
嘿
Hey!
站住
Stop!
站住 不然我开枪了
Stop, or I'll shoot!
操
Shit!
他当然已经死了
He's dead, of course.
上校
Colonel.
很抱歉你的士兵惨死街头
The death of your soldier was tragic.
但你这下明白面对的是什么罪犯了吧
But it does show you what kind of criminals we're facing.
先生们 能单独说几句吗
Gentlemen, if I may have a moment, please.
莱利先生
Mr. Riley.
这不仅是一场悲剧
This is much more than tragic.
敢杀我的人 绝对不可原谅
The killing of one of my men is utterly inexcusable.
这一切必须结束 马上结束
This has to end, and it has to end now.
相信我上校
Believe me, Colonel,
我也不想你再死人了
I don't want any more of your men dead.
所以我想了个办法把他们引出来
That's why I've devised a plan to flush them out
然后逮捕
and arrest them.
愿闻其详
I'm listening.
我们放火把他们逼出来
We burn them out.
天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
给房子点放把火 他们会尖叫着跑出来的
Set fire to the house, and they'll come squealin'.
所以我得到你允许了吗
Do I have your permission to proceed?
只要你不烧毁正整座城
So long as you don't burn down the whole goddamn town,
或是危及我的军队
or endanger any of my troops.
是的
Yes. -
我允许你这么做
You have my permission.
需要的话 你可以再喝一杯
Have another if it helps
日安 先生
Good day, sir.
伙计们 有人来了
Fellas! Someone's comin'!
这就对了 把房子点燃 小子们
That's it. Lighter up, boys.
让你们暖和暖和 比利
Gonna get warm in there, Billy!
走吧 杰西
Let's go, Jesse.
绕到后面去 绕到后面去
Go around the back! Go around the back!
快去拿水来
Someone get water, now!
干得好 伙计们
That's a good job, fellas! -
他们是罪有应得
They're gonna get what's comin'to'em.
治安官
Sheriff!
怎么啦
What?
是麦克斯温的大宅
McSween's?
是的 长官
Yes, Sheriff.
帮我锁门 好吗
Lock up for me, would ya?
是 长官
Yes, Sheriff.
操
Ah, fuck.
还有人过来 你听到了吗
There's more coming! You hear me?
让你的人到后面去
Get your boys over there around the back.
你们跑去多到马车后面
I want you boys to post up right behind this wagon.
走吧 小子们 上 上 上
Let'sgo, boys. Go. Go, go, go, go.
掩护我们
Cover us! -
上吧 小子们
Let's go, boys.
在这边
Here we go. -
好小子
Good lad!
妈的
Fuck.
火势在蔓延
This fire's spreading!
汤姆 快来帮我搬钢琴
Tom, help me move the piano!
好吧
Okay.
要小心
Careful, careful!
好的 站成一排 注意侧翼
AlI right, extended line. Keep the flanks.
让我们过去
Let us pass.
我奉命看守这里
I have my orders
任何人不得越过这条警戒线
not to let anyone past this cordon.
你本该保持中立的
You're supposed to be neutral.
不应该偏袒任何一方
You're not supposed to take sides.
那栋着火的房子里还有女人
And there are women inside that burning house.
你们要害我们女人
So why are you against us?
小姐 我重复一遍我的命令
Senorita, I can only repeat my orders.
那栋房子里有我们爱的人
There are people we love inside that house.
我们要去帮他们 让我们过去
We are going to help them. Let us pass!
不 回家去吧
No! Go to your homes.
-让我们过去  -不行
Let us pass! - No!
别逼我们使用必要的武力
We will use necessary force! -
你现在连女人都打了
You're hitting a woman now?
拦住他们 我命令你住手
Hold them back! I order you to stop!
-我将使用任何必要的武力  -够了
I'll use whatever force necessary. Enough!
多打些水来
Bring more water!
亚历山大 前面再多来点水
Alexander, we need more water up front!
-快点  -快点 快点
- Hurry, please! - Come on, quickly,
我们得把火扑灭
we gotta put these flames out!
前面多来点水灭火 拜托
We need more water in the front, please!
快点
Hurry up!
很高兴你们来了 孩子们
Glad to have you here, boys!
妈的 军队来了
Shit, the Army's here!
亚历山大 亚历山大
Alexander! Alexander!
什么 怎么了
What? What is it?
我们必须做点什么
We have to do something.
我们还能做什么
What else could we possibly do?
我要去找达德利上校 我要让他
I'm going to Colonel Dudley. I'm gonna ask him
结束这种疯狂行径
to stop this madness.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
他跟莱利是一条船上的
He's hand in glove with Riley.
他根本不会听你的 苏珊
He'll...he'll never listen to you. Susan!
苏珊 你会被杀掉的
Susan, you'll get killed.
达德利上校说他是来保护
Colonel Dudley told us that he was here to protect
妇女和儿童的 所以我必须去
women and children. So it's only right
找他讲讲道理 他会听我的
that I should try and talk to him. He'll listen to me.
听着 麦克斯温太太 你很有勇气
Look, Mrs. McSween, that's very courageous- -
我必须这么做 让我出去
I have to do this. I am going out!
你不能一个人出去
You cannot go out there alone.
我可以 我会的
I am. And I will.
好吧 我们需要一面白旗
Okay, we need a white flag.
给你
Here.
我和你一起去
Let me come with you.
不 亲爱的 你太年轻了
No, my dear, you're far too young.
没关系
It's okay.
苏珊 看着我 你要小心
Susan, look at me. You be careful.
比利
Billy.
是 女士
Yes, ma'am.
别开枪 有女人出来了
Hold your fire! There's a woman is comin'out!
好吧
All right.
暂停 别开枪
Hold it. Hold your firel
嘿
Hey!
熄火
Halt!
嘿 熄火 熄火
Hey, halt, halt.
嘿 别开枪
Hey, hold your firel
比利一探头出来 你就开枪
You see Billy's head, you shoot.
长官
Sir.
我要和达德利上校对话
I'd like to talk to Colonel Dudley.
加勒特治安官
Sheriff Garrett!
麦克斯温太太
Mrs. McSween.
你都该为自己害臊
You should be ashamed of yourself,
眼睁睁看着我房子被烧 你明知
allowing my house to be set on fire when you know
里面还有女人
there are women inside.
你要是不想房子被烧的话
If you don't want your house burned down,
就让里面的人出来
tell the men inside to come out.
我不想在玩猫捉耗子的游戏了
I am tired of chasing'em.
你本该是执法者
You are supposed to be a lawman,
本该保障人民权利
protecting the rights of the people.
但你却表现得像个罪犯
But you're behaving like a criminal.
真正的罪犯就在那座房子里
The criminals are inside that house.
而我今天就将一网打尽
And I will have them this day,
甭管是死了还是活着
alive or dead.
我要找达德利上校
I need to speak to Colonel Dudley.
我不会拦着你的
I'm not stoppin'you.
女士
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
没事了 中尉 下去吧
It's all right, Lieutenant. You're dismissed.
长官
Sir.
夫人 我想我知道你是谁
Madam, I believe I know who you are,
律师麦克斯温先生的妻子
the wife of Mr. McSween, the lawyer.
-我说的对吗  -很正确
Am I correct in that? - Yes, you are.
我想问问你的军队
Ah. And I would like to know
为什么从一开始就要进城
why your troops have come into town in the first place?
我丈夫说美国军队
My husband tells me that it is most irregular
介入民事纠纷 这很罕见
for the U. S. Army to get involved in civil affairs.
夫人 我带部队进驻林肯
Madam, I have brought my troops to Lincoln
是要保护妇女和儿童的安全
to protect the women and children.
可现在 两名妇女马上就要被活活烧死
But two women are now likely to be burned alive!
恐怕你的解释根本站不住脚
I'm afraid your explanation, Colonel Dudley,
达德利上校
is just too thin.
女士 我是美国陆军上校
Madam, I am a colonel in the United States Army,
我为国服务了23年
and I have served my nation for 23 years.
我的正直轮不到你来质疑
I will not have you question my integrity.
现在请你离开
Now I need you to leave.
不
No.
我知道你是个正直的人
I know you're a man of honor.
所以我恳求你救救我丈夫
I implore you to save my husband from death
不要让我家化为灰烬
and my home from burning.
治安官只是在履行职责
I cannot interfere with the sheriff
我不能干涉
in the execution of his duty.
你当然可以
Of course you can!
我不会的
I will not.
夫人 你丈夫窝藏了已知的罪犯
Madam, your husband is harboring known criminals,
身上还背负着逮捕令
with outstanding warrants for their arrest.
他们要是真想结束这场战争
If they wish for this battle to end,
只要向当局自首
they simply need to turn themselves in
就可以了
to the authorities.
我丈夫如果自首 肯定会被杀
If my husband did that, he would assuredly be killed.
达德利上校 我丈夫不是罪犯
Colonel Dudley, my husband is not the criminal.
墨菲和莱利先生才是真正的罪犯
It is Mr. Murphy and Mr. Riley who are the criminals here.
你的工作本该是保护我丈夫
And your job should be to protect my husband
而不是那些要杀他灭口的人
and not those who wish to kill him.
求你发发慈悲 看在上帝的份上
Have you no mercy? For the love of God.
我已经告诉过你了
I've already told you.
我进行干涉就是偏袒你
I will not interfere on your behalf.
日安 夫人
Good day to you, madam.
你确定要再回去吗
Are you sure you want to go back in there?
确定 这里是我家
Yes. It's my home.
-你没事吧  -没事 我很好
- Are you okay? - Yeah. Fine.
-他们没伤害你吧  -没有
- They didn't hurt you? - No.
上帝啊
My god.
吁
Whoa, whoa.
你笑什么笑
Who you smilin' at?
杰西
Jesse.
你觉得他们会投降吗
think they're gonna surrender?
他们别无选择
They've got no fuckin' choice.
他们就要被活活烧死了
They're about to be burned alive.
比利绝不会投降的
Billy ain't ever gonna surrender.
扯淡 这说不通 杰西
Well, that's crazy! It make no sense, Jesse.
你怎么就搞不明白 莱利
Why don't you ever get it, Riley?
你面对的是比利小子
You're talking about Billy the Kid!
比利小子
Billy the fuckin' Kid!
他和你不一样 和我也不一样
He's different from you, and he is different from me.
他身上没有一点说得通
He don't have to make sense.
现在房子只有一条出路 在后门
There's only one way out now: through the back door.
让你的人在墙后列队
You get your men to line up behind that wall.
如果他们举着白旗出来
If they come out with a white flag,
就把他们抓起来 要是没有
I'll arrest them. If not.
那将上演一场精彩的射击表演
it's gonna be one hell of a turkey shoot.
来吧
Come on.
走 走 走
Go, go, go, go.
低头
Heads down.
快 快 快 离开这里 快走
Go, go, go, go! Get out of here, go!
上
Go, go! -
袍使我躺在青草地上
He maketh me to lie down in green pastures...
汤姆 醒醒吧
Tom! Wake up!
快
Go!
他指引我走义路
He leadeth me in the paths of righteousness.
你们仨现在必须走
The three of you have to leave now.
-可是  -这是命令
- But, I- I- - - I'm not asking.
听我说 你得赶紧走 不然就太迟了
I'm telling you. You gotta go before it's too late.
不不不
No, no, no.
我会紧随其后 但你必须走了
I'll be right behind you. You have to leave.
麦克斯温先生
Mr. McSween.
麦克斯温先生 没时间了
Mr. McSween, there's no time.
我就在你后面
I'll be right behind you.
三个非战斗人员出来了 别开枪
Three non- combatants comin' out! Hold your fire!
他们出来了 别开枪
They're comin' out. Hold your firel
很好 平民出来了
AlI right, civilians comin' out.
不要开枪 不要开枪
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
别开枪
Hold your firel
别开枪 小子们
Don't shoot, boys.
嘿 这边 来这里
Hey, over here. Over here.
快点
Now.
注意窗户
Watch the windows.
放开我
Get off me!
来吧
Come on!
窗户 注意窗户 小子们
Windows! Watch the windows, boys!
听着 我们不能待在这里
Listen up, we can't stay here.
他们不会接受我们投降的 所以我们得离开这
And they won't let us surrender, so we gotta go.
你们都知道该怎么办
You all know the deal.
我们分成小组 迅速撤离
We go in small groups, move fast,
不要让自己成为显著目标
don't make yourself an easy target.
我们其余的人会掩护火力
The rest of us lay down and cover fire.
只要杰西的人一抬头
As soon as Jesse and his gang raise their heads,
你们就先开枪
you shoot first.
别让他们有开枪的机会
Keep their heads down.
只要撤到树林 我们就自由了
If we can make it to the woods, then we're free.
好吧 谁要上
AII right, who's goin'?
我们
We are.
好的 小子们 祝你们好运 我们就在后面
AII right, boys, Godspeed. We'll be right behind you.
把这个给我女儿 好吗 比利
Give this to my girl, will ya, Billy?
是 先生
Yes, sir.
-好的 你准备好了吗  -冲啊 兄弟们
AlI right. You ready? - Let's go, boys.
冲
Go! -
快 快 快
- Go, go, go!
快开枪啊
Get them, boys!
小心 比利 你的左边
Look out, Billy, on your left!
该死
Ah, shit!
别让他们抬头射击
Keep their heads down!
不要开枪
Don't shoot!
我投降 不要开枪
I surrender! Don't shoot!
我们不能那么干 兄弟们
That ain't gonna be us, boys.
我们不能那么干
- - That's not gonna be us.
好吧 行动要快 蹲着跑过去
AlI right. Move fast. Stay low.
-另一边见  -是的 你会的
- See you on the other side. Yes, you will.
是的 我虽然行过死荫的幽谷
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow
也不怕遭害 因为你与我同在
of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me;
你的杖 你的竿 都安慰我
thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.
-准备好了吗  -上
Ready? Go.
快 快 快
Go, go, go! -
Go, go, go!
来啊
Come on!
来啊 你们这些混蛋
Come on, you fuckers.
朝你爷爷开枪 来吧
Hit mel Come on!
来吧
Come on!
咱们走
Let's go!
等等
Wait! -
-你还好吗  -我很好
- You good? - Yeah, I'm good.
-贝克维斯 你还好吗  -怀特跑掉了
- Beckwith, you good? - Waite got away.
妈的
Ah! Fuck.
就现在
Now!
该死
Goddamn it!
善良和仁慈
Surely goodness and mercy
当然将伴随我一生一世
shall follow me all the days of my life.
我要住在耶和华的殿中 直到永远
And I will dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
来 麦克斯温 这个给你
Okay. McSween, you take this,
你拿起枪逃命去
and you run for your life.
我不想要枪 比利 不用
I don't want a gun, Billy. No.
我有圣经
I have my Bible.
它在这一刻的意义 比我一生中任何时刻都更重要
At this moment in time, more than at any other moment
我必须忠于我的信仰和信念
in my life, I must be true to my faith and my convictions.
好吧
AlI right.
你去吧
You're up.
不要开枪
Don't shoot!
我手无寸铁
I'm unarmed.
先生们
Gentlemen...
我是麦克斯温
Iam McSween.
妈的
Fuck!
是我杀了麦克斯温 奖赏是我的了
I'm the man who killed McSween! I claim the reward.
是啊 我会狠狠赏他的
Yeah, he's gonna get the reward, all right.
好了 小子们
AlI right, boys.
我们得撤了
We gotta go.
虽然机会微乎其微
It's a million- to- one chance.
我无悔与你们并肩作战 都准备好了吗
There's no one I'd rather go with. You ready?
上吧
Let's go!
好的
AlI right. -
天使与我相遇在十字路囗 与我相遇
♪Angels meet me At the crossroads, meet me ♪
天使与我相遇在十字路口 与我相遇
比利小子出来了
It's the Kid!
天使与我相遇在十字路口 与我相遇
♪Angels meet me At the crossroads, meet me ♪
让罪人免费通行
♪Don't charge a sinner Any toll ♪
天使与我相遇在十字路口 与我相遇
♪Angels meet me At the crossroads, meet me ♪
让罪人免费通行
♪Don't charge a sinner Any toll ♪♪
他杀了贝克维斯
He killed Beckwith!
走吧
Go.
快他妈的走吧
Fucking go.
比利
Billy.
我们试着去帮你了
We tried to help.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
杜尔西尼亚和我 还有其他一些女人
Dulcinea and I and some of the other women
跑到林肯镇 想要去帮忙
decided to go into Lincoln to see if we could help.
真的吗
Is that true?
我们想帮忙 但军队阻止了我们
We wanted to help, but the Army stopped us.
我们都很生气
We were so angry.
我们尽力了
We tried.
我知道
I know.
你现在打算怎么办 比利
What are you going to do now, Billy?
说实话 我还不知道
Truthfully, I don't know yet.
我们又成了亡命之徒
We're outlaws again.
踏上了逃亡
On the run.
莱利和加勒特肯定还会继续追捕我们的
No doubt Riley and Garrett will organize a hunt.
所以
So, uh...
我跟查理明天一早就得走了
Charlie and I should leave in the morning.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
你今天很勇敢
You were brave today.
我想要讨回正义
I wanted justice.
为了我的父母
For my parents...
我可怜的弟弟
my poor brother.
一切都是那么艰难 比利
It's been so hard, Billy.
可现在 我觉得我有了活下去的理由
But now I believe I have a reason to live for.
我有了你
I have you.
嘿
Hey.
我们会熬过去的
We're gonna get through this.
你和我
You and me.
我爱你 比利
I love you, Billy.
我爱你
I love you.
再见了 谢谢你 胡安
Goodbye. Thank you, Juan.
你是个好人 一个很好的人
You're a good man. A good man.
谢谢您
Thank you.
祝您一路平安 再见
Have a safe journey, and farewell.
谢谢你
Thank you.
二位早上好啊
Well, top of the mornin' to you two.
你闻到了吗
Do you smell that?
崭新的一天 就该是这个味道
That's the crisp air of a fresh new day.
就是他害死了我丈夫
He's the man that I blame for my husband's death.
我担心他也会杀了我
I fear that he'll try and kill me too,
但我不会被吓倒
but I won't be intimidated.
绝不会被这种人渣吓倒
Not by scum like that.
那您打算做什么 夫人
So what are you going to do, Senora?
我要去拉斯维加斯
I'm going to Las Vegas.
我要请个好律师 起诉莱利
I'm going to hire a good lawyer to prosecute Riley
为我丈夫讨回公道
and bring justice to my husband.
他一直都相信 真理和正义必胜
He always believed that truth and justice will prevail,
我也是
and so do I.
治安官
Sheriff.
上校
Colonel.
治安官
Sheriff.
没想到会有这么多人的生命毁于一旦
I had not thought to see so many lives undone.
这就是我们林肯人的作风
That has been the way of it here in Lincoln.
可怜的贝克维斯
Poor Beckwith
你知道是谁杀了他 对吧
You know who killed him, don't you?
比利杀了他
It was Billy who killed him.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
你一点都不伤心吗 杰西
Ain't you got any feelings, Jesse?
我们和贝克一起共事了很久
We rode with Beckwith a long time.
没 没啥伤心的
No, not really.
我要是死了 他也不会伤心的 对吧
Like, he wouldn't have any feelings for me, now would he?
他当然会
Yeah, sure he would.
不会
No.
我们唯一的相同之处 就是金钱
Only thing we all have in common is money.
把感情抛在脑后 我们才能成功
We leave our feelings behind so we can make it.
这就是这一切的意义
That's what all this is about.
金钱 是吗
Money, huh?
怎么啦
What?
你不喜欢钱吗 杰西
You don't like money, Jesse?
说什么傻话 奥林杰
Don't be stupid, Olinger.
小心安葬他
You be careful with him.
既然那些罪犯已被赶走
Now that you've flushed these criminals out,
治安官 是时候翻过这一篇
Sheriff, it's time to press on,
画上句点了
get the job done.
至于我 我觉得自己这个中间人
As for myself, I feel like I have been an honest broker
当得还算成功 我已经命令部队
in this situation. And I have already
收拾东西 打道回府了
ordered my troops to pack up and head back to the barracks.
谢谢您的帮助 上校
I appreciate all the help, Colonel.
别担心 我们会
And fear not, we will find
追踪并逮捕那些漏网之鱼的
and arrest the remaining criminals.
这话说的漂亮治安官
Well, that is all well and good, Sheriff.
但事实是 比利小子是从你手里逃跑的
But the fact remains that you let Billy the Kid escape.
不管他到哪儿 都会继续
And wherever he is, he will continue
给你和国家带来麻烦
to cause trouble to you and this country.
治安官 我强烈建议你
Sheriff, I strongly advise you
找到他 除掉他
to hunt him down and remove him,
将他永远从美国人心中抹去
forever, from the American imagination.